Good morning and welcome to D Program
with Ted Rall and John Kiriakou. It's
Veterans Day, November 11th, 2025. Thank
you so much for joining us. John, happy
Veterans Day.
>> Happy Veterans Day. You know what? And
because it's Veterans Day, I want to
give a shout-out to some veterans who
are important to me. First of all, my
dad who hated literally every second
that he was in the military and made us
promise not to have the VFW do the
21-gun salute at his funeral, which we
did anyway.
My dad, Chris Kiriakou, Corporal Chris
Kiriakou.
But I've got three cousins on my mom's
side. Um
Uh Zane Argeris, Zane Sofis, Michael
Sofis. All of them were in the Marines.
All of them were in Vietnam and were
seriously like highly decorated heroes.
We're all proud of them. And my
brother-in-law, Spiro, who spent um
several tours of duty in Iraq during the
first Gulf War and the second. 100%
disabled veteran because of his service.
So happy Veterans Day to all those guys.
Wow, that's that's quite a military
family you have there.
>> We were poor people. There was no other
way out of Warren, Ohio.
Well, you know, anything to get out of
Warren, Ohio, for sure.
>> me about it. My my father
was a a civilian in the US Air Force.
Before that, he made his way up to first
lieutenant and then they he migrated
over to the civilian and became a
a very well-known aeronautical engineer.
The father of the modern Air Force, if
you Google him,
it will say. He's got a He's got a
building named after him at
Wright-Patterson Air Force Base.
>> Oh my heavens. Rall Hall. Wow. Nothing
like rhyming.
My my big veteran in my family is my
is my grand my French grandfather. He's
a He's a French veteran. So formerly, he
was a communist in the French
Resistance, but then he signed but then
he uh you know, ultimately, they were
merged into the FFI, the Forces
Françaises de l'Intérieur, and then they
they're they're considered even though
they were irregulars. They were brought
in in 1945 and declared to have been
retroactively formal members of the
French military who qualified for
pensions and
the whole thing.
>> name is on the Arc de Triomphe. Um
>> Oh my god, Ted.
>> He's He's a true hero of World War II.
That's that's a bonafide hero right
there.
He was. Yeah. And and there are stories
and then we could do an entire show, I'm
sure, on either of any of our relatives
just
about their military service. So cool.
So yeah, for for the veterans out there,
thank you. I never say this. Thank you
for your service, but thank you for your
service.
Okay, so we have a lot to talk about.
South Asia is blowing up.
We've got explosions in in both India in
the in the both the capitals of India
and Pakistan.
Two nuclear It's never good when two
nuclear powers neighboring each other
who fought several wars before are
blaming each other for terrorist
attacks.
Trump is going before the US Supreme
Court. I really want to I'm curious on
your thoughts about this. I have no idea
what you'll think. Jean Carroll verdict.
He owes her over 80 million dollars from
this verdict. I had some problems with
that verdict with that case, to say the
least.
>> There were a lot of unanswered
questions. And it's really old.
So I mean, it's hard to see how you
could launch a defense or even a
prosecution. And last but not least, you
know, we predicted when the war in Gaza
started to wind down. I think we could
just say it's starting to wind down.
That it wouldn't take long before the
before atrocities started coming to
light. That's already happening. The ITF
IDF soldiers who feel awful about what
they were told to do or what they saw
other soldiers do are starting to
testify about what they did and what
they saw. And they said that there was
just This is not surprising, but it's
it's good to have it on record that it
was a free-for-all. That they were told
that you could pretty much just shoot
anyone between 20 and 40, especially if
they were a male just for walking
around. If they were walking too slow,
they were a target. If they were walking
too fast, they were a target. If they
were two one person lagging behind two
others, they were a target. So
Anyway, as always, if you're in the
group chat in the live chat in Rumble or
on YouTube, please chime in with your
questions and everything. Um Salone, and
thank you for your donations over on
YouTube. We are we funded. Just a
reminder, we don't need any more money
for Robbie, although it's more than
welcome.
I will put up that URL in a second.
But Robbie is fully funded for the month
of November and thank you very much for
your support there. Thanks for the two
bucks, Tobby J. Happy Veterans Day to
you, too.
So 2324,
thanks again for the generous
contribution of 20 bucks.
Happy Veterans Day to all who served. Do
we think Sergey Lavrov is in a gulag
right now? And do you think Putin was
nervous because of his influence?
I don't I don't think he's in a gulag. I
don't think Putin was nervous. I think
there is something something happened.
Something was said or done that seems to
have pushed
Lavrov out of the you know, the
innermost circle. Temporarily, [snorts]
maybe. I don't know. But no, I don't
think so. I don't think Lavrov's in any
kind of danger.
I think the worst thing that could
happen to him is that he's he's told
that it's time to retire. He's old.
>> He's old, yeah. And he you know, he's
not wearing his age as well as Putin is.
So
>> No, that's right. I'm going to look to
see how old Lavrov is. I'd have to I'd
have to say he's 75.
>> Oh, I was going to say 72, but he
doesn't look like he and vodka are total
strangers.
>> Yeah, I would agree with that. Um
>> Yeah. Hyperneurotic over on the Rumble
chat, thank you for the five bucks.
Semper Fidelis, happy Veterans Day.
Best show around, praying that John gets
a pardon and a presidential Medal of
Freedom. You're as much of a veteran as
us. Angel Follow Law,
thank you for the five bucks, also. Um
and I got to give Rebellious Rainbow
Unicorn her props here. Sorry, Manya the
Cat, also.
Manya the Cat said not to spoil the
mood, but I I shudder every time Vietnam
War veteran is celebrated. My parents
had to evacuate Hanoi many times because
of the bombings as infants. Fair. That
is fair.
Yeah, that's fair. Uh okay, so let's get
to it.
What do we want to talk about first?
Let's talk about India and Pakistan
because that looks like it's getting
worse by the hour. Yeah.
So yesterday, we talked briefly about
about this bombing in Delhi that killed
people, that injured a lot. And we
speculated based on nothing but our own
analysis that it was probably Kashmiri
separatists. I think at this point, it
doesn't really matter who it was.
Other than
whoever it was needs to back off because
things are going to get worse quickly.
In the meantime,
the Pakistani Taliban, which is a an
indigenous Pakistani group that allies
itself with the Afghan Taliban because
it says that the Pakistani government is
not Islamic enough, launched an attack
in Islamabad
>> [clears throat]
>> aimed solely at civilians.
And it's like What is it? A dozen dead
and two dozen wounded so far.
This is the first attack directed solely
against civilians in more than 10 years.
But this is what the Pakistani Taliban
and ISIS-K do in Pakistan. They will
attack Shia Muslim mosques. Mhm.
>> They'll attack police stations. They
tried to attack a month ago um
a
a training academy for for teenage
police cadets. They were They were
repulsed
in Pakhtunkhwa,
Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, but what used to be
called the Northwest Frontier Province.
So this is
this is not looking good on either side.
The Pakistani government immediately
blamed India for this attack, saying
that it was India that supported the
Pakistani Taliban. Of course, the
Indians are blaming the Pakistanis for
the bombing in Delhi. And as you said in
the intro, Ted, when the two sides are
nuclear powers,
nothing good can come of this. They need
to start talking
and maybe working together
and coming to an agreement to not not
arm, train, and finance terrorist groups
that are attacking each other.
Right. [snorts] Well, I mean, Pakistan,
I thought was really interesting, but
their spin was that they actually blamed
India for Afghan They They said it's
Afghans who work with the Pakistani
Taliban. Um that
is 92%
probably not true, right?
>> Yeah, I would think so, yeah. Yeah,
okay.
>> Because what do they get out of it? What
do they accomplish out of this? You You
go You go to you know, whatever, a hotel
or In this case, it was a court
building.
And you blow yourself up and kill two
dozen people. Okay. What What do you get
out of that? No No policies are going to
change. Your cousin's not going to be
released from prison.
It's It's just it's just murder.
Senseless murder. There's nothing else
you can call it.
Although, I mean, you know, to to play
devil's advocate, you know, this was
part of the this was a big part of the
war against US occupation forces in
Afghanistan for 20 years was exactly
those kind of just tactics that pre you
know, that never existed in Afghanistan
before 2001, right? That was suicide
bombing was not a thing in in
Afghanistan. They
They did every other kind of war
>> That's right.
>> but not that. Um and and and seems like
that tactic, you know, sort of like it
came out of Iraq, it migrated into South
Asia, and now it's here say, but
obviously there's been like there was
the
the the attack at the Taj Hotel in
Mumbai. I mean, this has been a a
back-and-forth thing generally speaking
Pakistan has always tended to be more
guilty of this. Yeah. overwhelmingly,
right? Yes. And then India's to me where
you blame India is that they tend have a
tendency to turn up the temperature,
right? Like the government of Prime
Minister Modi is you know, basically you
know, he he's a nationalist and this
plays into his narratives about, you
know, and using Pakistan as the bette
noire. And you know, I mean it's
I got to say,
you know, when you when you go to India,
right? Like you you'll people will say
they hate Gandhi because he presided
over the partition and we're still
[__] fighting over this [__] now.
And it's it's just you're right. I mean,
what ultimately needs to happen is for
India and Pakistan to get together and
and cut the [__] Um Yes. you know, and
and they're also kind of I think
unwittingly being used as proxies by
without any question. Yes. So Yes. Yes,
definitely. I agree with that
completely.
So it's well we're we're going to follow
that. You know, there were two incidents
in Pakistan by the way, right? The
the district court in Islamabad was
blown up the outside. 12 people died, 27
injured right in the middle of the lunch
hour. Um and you know, that that almost
certainly is you know, I would say
Pakistani Taliban, right? Almost
certainly. Um but the I don't think
India had anything to do with it. Um the
Red Fort thing, I mean, you know,
they're they're going to they're going
to react to this with sort of a post
9/11 kind of attitude. They just invoked
Modi just invoked the Unlawful
Activities Prevention Act which allows
basically the suspension of civil
liberties under Indian law,
a lot more spying on Indian citizens and
so on. So this is a great opportunity
for it's like a Reichstag fire kind of
crackdown.
Man, this is not good. India and
Pakistan are no strangers to to
scrapping it out. But again, they both
have nuclear weapons. And I'm going to
go on record again, despite what the
Pakistani media is saying about me,
the Pakistanis will get their asses
kicked in a in a conventional war.
Well, they have every single time,
right? The Pakistanis have mixed it up
with the Indians on three separate
occasions. That's right. Most recently,
it's very personal for me, John, cuz I
was literally there. I helped break the
story of the Kargil conflict. It was an
it was an accident. I mean, my my friend
Cole and I were on a bus on the
Karakoram Highway.
We crossed the border from Xinjiang in
China on the bus and the first thing
that we noticed was that on the
Pakistani side of the border, the border
outpost was abandoned. Um you never see
that. It was just it's a it's a trailer
with like a Pakistani flag on it. And we
walked inside and they were gone and
it's like it's like the movie where the
teacup was still warm and the guy had
taken off. And we we drove for the
better part of 24 hours before we
encountered any human beings. And then
finally we started seeing Afghan
Taliban, you know, this is 1999,
marching along the side of the streets
and then came into a little village and
there had just been some kind of battle
there, a small battle. There's some dead
cows and some dead, you know, some some
a few dead bodies. And then we just kept
going. saw and then it was like, oh god,
the Taliban are here. And it's like
we're in Afghan we're in Pakistan. This
is the northern areas as they called it
at the time.
>> felt so far from home as I did there. Oh
my god.
>> Never anywhere in the world did I feel
so far away from home as the Northwest
Frontier Province. Agreed. And we got
pulled off the bus and they were like by
the Taliban. And and I and they were
like, you should know better than to
come to to Afghanistan. I said, this
isn't Afghanistan, this is Pakistan. And
he goes, it's Afghanistan now.
Oh my god.
>> was right at the same time that right
like basically a week later when I was
in Islamabad,
Musharraf overthrew the the Sharif
government and turned out that Musharraf
appears to have made some kind of deal
with the Taliban to basically open the
border and allow the Taliban to come in
and fight the Indians as proxies and
that started this high altitude 1999
third Kashmir war aka the Kargil
conflict. Um
And it was just like but again, the
Pakistanis never stood a chance.
You know.
>> No, they didn't stand a chance.
No. You know, what what is dangerous
right now
well, it's and it's what was dangerous
in the in past conflicts as well
is that the the the Taliban government
and the Indians are very friendly.
Very friendly. Do you remember
it must have been 2002,
I guess. I know what you're going to
say. About the big bombing in
Afghanistan? Mhm. At the Indian Embassy?
I mean,
the crater was 30 ft deep. Yeah.
Yeah. And and but there's been there's
been ties, right? I mean, like for
example, there was the Air India flight
that was hijacked
to Taliban
Afghanistan and the Taliban took care of
it. Um I've always thought it was a
curious relationship because, you know,
it is called the Hindu Kush mountains,
Right.
>> of Hindus.
You know, I mean
it's weird like the Afghans really seem
to
you know, they don't they really hate
the everything that the Indians are
about in terms of their religion and all
that, but they don't seem to dislike the
Indian people that much. I think that's
exactly right.
Yes. And and of course their culture is
all over the place, right? Like all of
the Bollywood movies are all over
Sometimes before they're released in in
India, they the bootlegs make their way
to Afghanistan. It's the craziest thing.
John, the first movie I saw that was
ever released after the fall of the
Taliban was playing at a movie theater
in Kabul. I saw it open and it was
I was driving by in a taxi and it was
AK-47 which was a Bollywood movie. And I
was and the and the guy in the taxi
driver completely stone-faced goes, I
love that movie. I feel like I could it
really talks to me. And I'm like, you're
Afghan, of course AK-47 speaks to you.
The country's awash in them.
>> [laughter]
>> I
you know, I was
I know that you know this, but I was
sent to Afghanistan by
Paramount Pictures in 2007
to rescue these children who had
appeared in the movie The Kite Runner
and their families because so many
Afghans are so simple
that they didn't know the difference
between a movie and reality. They they
thought that when they saw these bootleg
copies of The Kite Runner that this was
this was a depiction of reality
and they set out to kill the children
who appeared in the movie.
And so the studio had to get them out.
Yeah, Afghans are not
complicated
>> [laughter]
>> sophisticated individuals.
>> No, not they're but they're wild they
but they I have a they have like a
there's something about them that I love
is that they're the only people I've
ever met and there may be others on the
planet cuz I've hardly been everywhere,
but they have the these wild eyes. Like
they're wild. Like they're they're like
they have something in in that human
beings don't have anywhere else that's
been like tamed out of us. You know what
I mean? Like this sort of like ferocity.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, they're perfectly happy to pick up
that AK-47
>> [clears throat]
[laughter]
>> and say, what did you just say?
Totally. Yeah. And and I love their
their dark cynicism, too. I mean, I was
looking for an old fixer from nine years
previous and the guy's like, how long's
it been? And I go, nine years. He goes,
nine years? He's probably dead. This is
Afghanistan.
Oh my god.
>> [laughter]
>> And he was serious, too. Oh my god.
It's it's pretty crazy.
All right, so let's see here. We have
I'm trying to I'm just trying to like We
By the way, we get Robbie back on Monday
and not a day too soon, I got to say.
And Robbie's in the chat. Robbie, we
love you. We
we need you. Can't do it without you.
Well, we can do it without you, just not
well. Um
Anyways, do we do we want to talk about
E. Jean Carroll? Yeah, let's talk about
E. Jean Carroll.
All right, so E. Jean Carroll,
obviously, she was the writer for
various magazines. She was a columnist
in New York City.
>> [snorts]
>> Um and back in the mid-90s, she
ran into Donald Trump. This part's all
like not in question. She ran into
Donald Trump in the street like an
episode of Sex and the City.
And it's like, hey Donald. And somehow
they decided to walk to Bergdorf Goodman
together. Maybe she was going to shop,
maybe he was going to shop, but one
decided to tag along with the other. One
thing led to another. They end up in a
dressing room at Bergdorf Goodman, which
if you're not familiar with New York
City, is a huge luxurious Fifth Avenue
department store. And you know, you
might be thinking about like say Macy's
or or someplace like that. It's not like
that. Um so the the dressing
>> example, I'm sorry to interrupt you.
RT gave me a ton of money a few years
ago because I lost all this weight and
they told me, "Here's $10,000, go buy
new clothes." Nice. Yeah, it was very
generous of them. So I went out and I
bought a bunch of clothes. I happen to
be in New York and I went to Bergdorf
Goodman's. Mhm. And I was just looking
for a couple of polo shirts.
Just regular polo shirts. Right.
>> $700
per polo shirt. In the '80s, I went
shopping for a pillow and I accidentally
bumped bumped into there cuz I was
working at a bank nearby.
And the pillows were 400 bucks.
And they weren't special. They're not
like, you know, they don't they don't
give you oral sex. It's like they're
just pillows.
I
>> [laughter]
>> was like, what the [__]
>> Oh my god. No, yeah. So and also, so
this is key to the story. And anyway, by
all by all accounts, Carol and uh well,
not Trump. Trump claims that he didn't
even know her. Right.
>> We know that's not true.
>> It's not true. And uh that basically
there's no question. They ended up in
that in that uh in that room together.
Uh they fooled around. Um she said that
there was uh penetrated Basically, she
was all in until he wanted penetrated uh
penetrated sex. That happened against
her will. So she said she'd been raped.
She kept it all to herself, although she
did contemporaneously
uh mention it to a few friends. And uh
and within the you know, a year or two
after the incident. And then
uh and then years later um you know,
during the whole lawfare period uh
during the Biden administration, I guess
Carol probably thought this was her
chance. Who knows? What Who knows why?
Maybe it was simply a matter of like I
finally had enough and I'm going to sue.
Long story short, she sues him. And
obviously, the statute of limitations
has long expired. But she sues him in
civil court. New York State had just
passed That's probably why she did it.
Uh outgoing Governor Cuomo had just
signed a one-year window for old
eliminating the temporarily suspending
the statute of limitations for civil
lawsuits uh related to sexual misconduct
in New York State.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so she filed that suit. That's
probably why. And um
And she won. Uh she kicked his ass six
ways till Sunday.
Um and so she was, you know, this is a
civil suit based on the preponderance of
the evidence, which means that the jury
has to think more or less that it's 50%
likely to have happened. Um this
ultimately $5 million jury finding of
sexual abuse and defamation, the
defamation being that he denied that it
happened.
>> Right. And the $83 million defamation
add-on when he appealed, the judge said,
"Oh, you didn't think $5 million is
enough? Uh we'll give you $83 million
more." So he owes her nearly $90
million. He's in front of the US Supreme
Court, John. Um I don't know what
happens there and I am going to
speculate and say I don't know that
there's been any very many credible uh
you know, allegations of actual rape
against Donald Trump. Um creepiness up
the ass, but not not rape. Um
So
>> the same way. But I have a serious
[__] problem with the fact that any
human being in the United States can be
dragged before a court more than 25
years after an alleged incident when
it's absolutely impossible to gather,
you know, evidence, um to gather
witnesses. Uh you know, if if he had a
Let's say he wasn't there. Yeah.
>> be way to How is he going to be able to
prove that he has an alibi, right? Like,
"Oh, I was actually in Florida that
weekend." or whatever. I mean, he can't
He There's just no way to defend
yourself. And when you're in a civil
suit, you really kind of need to defend
yourself. It's not really like the
burden of proof is all on the accuser.
>> Mhm. So um he's What do you think is I
think I know what's going to happen
here, but I think the Supremes are going
to toss it. What do you think? I think
the Supremes are going to toss it as
well.
You know,
the Supreme Court doesn't like to get
involved in these
kind of more petty he said, she said
things. They get involved where there
are major and serious constitutional
issues at play. And there's no
constitutional issue at play here. I
think that
I think that this jury
award is outrageous. They did it
They did it at this number because it's
Donald Trump and he has plenty of money.
But um Yeah.
And also, he it was like it was like the
time to gang up on Donald Trump and it
was It was.
Yes, but I I don't think the Supreme
Court is going to be at all interested
in this kind of a case.
I mean, could they just um could they
just refuse to hear it? Oh, yeah. In
fact, they refuse to hear 90-something
percent of cases. Mhm. Yeah. Anybody,
literally anybody can appeal anything to
the Supreme Court. And
a little factoid, you don't have to go
through the process of going to the
district court, then the circuit court,
then the Supreme Court. You can just go
straight to the Supremes. Another
factoid that people don't know is that
your your appeal is not based on the
justice or injustice of the lower court
decision.
>> That's right.
>> on a constitutional question. So you
have It's a very short brief usually.
And you basically just go to the court
and you say,
uh what happened here um raises uh some
unresolved constitutional question that
we would like you, the court, to weigh
in on.
That's right.
>> And so I don't know what constitutional
issue there would be. Is it statute of
limitations or
I don't know. But even that
>> me would be the defa- I don't know if
it's a constitutional issue, but like I
think it's like sophistry to say that
denying guilt in a case can uh can open
you up to a defamation claim. I mean, at
that rate, I mean,
literally Why I have to
>> half of all everyone who's accused of a
crime who denies it is guilty of perjury
and defamation against the victim,
right? It doesn't make any sense to me
at all.
None. Yeah, it's it's So we'll see, but
on on the other hand, I don't know that
there's a constitutional issue.
>> No. He should probably just
pay the money and move on. Just move on.
I don't know. If if he didn't do it, I
wouldn't pay. My
My mom taught me never admit to anything
you didn't do.
>> can seize, you know, a building or
something.
Well, John, so here
Here's a
Here's a question. Uh thank you very
much, Toby, for your five Australian
dollars. Um I think he might need six
Australian
>> [laughter]
>> dollars to answer this question, John.
Based on all your CIA training and
frontline experience, what have you
learned to be the most profound truths,
plural, about human nature?
That's a big [__] question.
>> It's a big question and I'm going to be
some something of a downer here
and say that um
that human nature is an ugly thing. This
is what I discovered, that people will
do hideous things if they believe that
they are the good guys in a conflict.
And you can never trust
that a person's humanity will will
control their uglier impulses.
I saw people do horrible things. We were
going out for a raid one night in
Pakistan.
Uh there was this guy, Dan, who was
working for me. And I liked Dan. He was
a nice enough guy.
Um and I said, "Dan, strap up. Let's go.
We got to get going." Like, "Where's
your gun?" And he said, "Oh, I can't
go." I said, "Why not?"
He said, "I'm not allowed to carry a
gun." I said, "Why?"
He said, "I beat my wife." I was like,
"Oh, okay."
So he didn't go. Because there's a rule
at the CIA, if you're accused credibly
of beating your wife or beating your
spouse, you can't carry a gun. And if
you can't carry a gun, you can't go on
the raid. So he just kind of sat back at
the office and waited for us to come
back.
Um and that was a little thing.
Otherwise, you know,
I I've said many many many times that
the CIA committed atrocities, crimes
against humanity.
And and I've called out the people who
did it. But my my ugly conclusion is
that people will default to the war
crime
rather than to default to doing the
right thing. That's the ugliest thing
I've learned about human nature.
It's uh yeah, I I was you know, when you
when you said that, I was literally just
thinking, you know, I love to collect
propaganda and and military ephemera.
And the belt buckle, I don't have one
yet. Uh but the Nazi belt buckle said in
German, right? Like God is with us. God
is on our side. And it has the swastika
on it. And everybody thinks that like
if, you know, they're if if it's
supporting their side, they can do
whatever they want and they want and it
it's justified. Yeah.
>> Um you know, in the in the course of a
quote-unquote higher calling. Um very
very good question here. Um
Jennifer PO is asking why we didn't talk
about uh the fact that Nicolas Sarkozy
Yes.
>> of got out of the can yesterday.
>> He was only in for like a week, wasn't
he?
>> Three weeks. Okay. Probably felt like
two and a half. All right.
>> [laughter]
>> He was in so- He was in solitary,
apparently, the entire time.
>> Uh you would have to be. And they
Really? Why? Just because he's so high
profile?
>> his ass kicked otherwise. I mean, who
wouldn't want to be the guy who, you
know, beat Nicolas Sarkozy so badly that
his eyeball popped out or something? He
does have a very punchable face, too.
Yeah, he does. And he's a very small
man.
And you know, people think of France as
like this really like sort of mellow,
but the prisons are are have a terrible
reputation there.
Um you know, it's it's very dangerous.
Um
So, I could So, I I'm I don't even
understand why the [__] they released
him, right? Basically, it's like his
defense team basically just said,
"Please release him pending trial."
And they said, "Okay."
And that's it.
I mean, it's it I guess it's sort of
like it's France, it's class, membership
has its privileges. May I ask you
something, too? Several times
when explaining my legal situation Mhm.
to Europeans, I'll give you an example.
One night I I was invited to speak at
the Luxembourg Film Festival. Bunch of
us went out afterwards, and I happen to
be sitting next to the Minister of
Justice of Luxembourg. Guy was like half
my age.
But,
he went on and on about the French
system, that how how far superior the
French legal system was to what we had
in the United States or what the Brits
have in the UK. And he said he said
something very interesting. I have no
idea if it's true, but I'm hoping you
can tell me. He said that the job of the
attorneys, both the prosecuting
attorneys and the defense attorneys, is
to get to the truth. Yes. And so,
they'll they'll do the investigation
together. Mhm. Then, they'll negotiate,
you know, a deal, or if they can't
negotiate the deal, then it goes to
trial. Is that true? That is true. And
in fact, the formal term is uh for a
trial is that it's a judicial inquiry.
This goes back to um the to the
Napoleonic code, right? Um and and the
idea is like prob- I really am sad that
it's not yet available in the United
States, but an officer and a spy, which
is the most uh recent um film by Oh my
god, uh
you know, the disgraced director Oh, um
uh
um Roman Polanski. Yeah, Polanski. It's
Polanski's most recent movie. It came
out um I think in 2019 or something.
It's been banned in the West and the
United States because uh you know,
because he was Me Too'd so ferociously,
but the movie's fantastic. Um and it's
based on the Dreyfus affair and the
Dreyfus trial, and they showed this
process of of how it's a it's a it's a I
mean, obviously he was railroaded, but
it is a it is and that's part of what
what went wrong was that like there was
misconduct on the part of the
prosecution. They weren't really
interested in the truth, as Jack
Nicholson would say. Mhm.
And uh the But, that is how the system
is supposed to work. Obviously, you
know, uh the hum- human beings, you
know, err. But, yeah, no, I mean, that
is that's the ideal. I mean, the I you
know, it's it's not really adversarial
uh the way ours is. I mean, in our
system, you basically spin the facts in
accordance with your side of the
equation. Uh you know, if if you're a
defense attorney, your your your client
is pure as the driven snow. If you're
the prosecutor, they're the devil.
It's not like that there. It's more like
we we want to find out what actually
happened here. Now, that said, there's
one thing that I really hate about the
French system, which is you have no
presumption of innocence.
So Interesting. That's that's pretty
ugly. Yeah. Pre- I mean, actually,
presumption of innocence is kind of rare
in uh in the world's legal systems.
It's It's one of the things that used to
make the United States special.
Wow. That's rough.
Oh, well, and I I don't know if you if
Well, Anna Kirk- Sally Kirkland, who's
an actress just died.
>> just saw that. Yeah, she was in The
Sting. I remember her in The Sting. She
was quite good. The Sting is, you know,
one of those movies I've been meaning to
go back to. I saw it when it came out
when I was a kid, like 10 years old. You
are going to love it as much as you did
the first time you saw it. I just
rewatched it like in the last year, and
I was like, "Dang, I forgot what a great
movie this was."
>> Robert Redford
and Paul Newman. So good. Yeah. Yeah.
Got to got to see it again. All right.
So, I was just I I did the Sorry to get
off track, but I did the Dalton Fisher
podcast yesterday. It's going to come
out next week. And we got sidetracked
onto the onto the subject of movies, uh
specifically science fiction movies.
Mhm. And um
he
he he had never heard of Soylent Green.
What? That's what I said. Are you
kidding me?
>> [laughter]
>> I said, "It's one of the greatest sci-fi
movies ever made and one of the most
important films of the 1970s." And he
said, "Oh my god, I love 70s and 90s
movies. They were so great." I said,
"Yeah, but especially 70s movies." Even
my kids bought me this coffee table book
called
called The Stewardesses Flying the
Plane, Movies of the 1970s.
Um and I told him what Soylent Green was
all about, and he's like, "Oh my god, it
sounds great." I said, "Well, I looked
it up while we were talking. I said,
"It's available on Amazon Prime. You
have to pay $3.99 for it, but it's worth
the the $3.99."
And [snorts] I said, "The only thing
they got wrong, because, you know, this
took place in the in the far future, 19
I'm sorry, 2015
it took place in 2015.
So, [snorts] they're imagining all these
different things.
Uh Charlton Heston worked in what they
called the megalopolis, which was just
this giant city from Boston to
Washington. You couldn't tell when you
leave one city you enter the next Oh,
that's kind of like analogous to what
they're the Saudis are building, right?
>> Yes. That crazy A giant city outside
Jeddah. It's called The Line, I think.
>> Yeah, The Line, cuz it's all in a line,
cuz they have to supply water to it. So,
um I said, "The only thing they got
wrong
was, you know, they're in these they're
in these police cars that sort of float,
you know, they're like almost like
spaceships. They float just off the
ground. You don't need tires, that kind
of thing."
>> Hovercraft, yeah. Hovercraft, but every
time Charlton Heston needed to talk to
his police station, he had to pull over
and use a payphone.
>> [laughter]
>> It's so funny. Uh John, I'm going to put
up this question then and then read an
ad uh while you think about it. This is
from Fuso. Thanks for the buck. Does
Egyptian intel work with Mossad like as
in international uh assassinations?
And I'm going to go ahead and uh and hit
this ad. Here we go. Okay.
Um this is uh
oldie but a goodie. Still haven't tried
1775 coffee? Now's your shot. The 1775
starter kit just dropped, only 1,000
units. You're getting the bold dark
roast that hits hard, the smooth medium
roast, and the vitality mushroom coffee
for clean energy and laser focus, no
crash. All single origin, small batch,
toxin-free, and mold-free. Plus, you're
also getting a gold spoon clip, because
freedom isn't scooped with plastic, a
frother strong enough to stir up your
coffee and your mother-in-law's
opinions, and a black 1775 tumbler. $170
worth of coffee and gear yours for $99.
This is for the ones who've been
watching through 1775 blow up on Rumble
wondering if it's actually worth it.
Spoiler, it is. Go to
1775coffee.com/studio
and grab your starter kit before they're
gone. Bold beans, clean fuel, and a
morning routine that stands for
something just like Rumble does.
John.
Um
we were talking about uh
Mossad and Egypt. Uh there is uh surface
cooperation between Mossad and the
Egyptian uh GID, the General
Intelligence Directorate, where GID will
tell Mossad, "Look, you've got a problem
with some Palestinians at the Rafah
Crossing.
Palestinians in Cairo are talking about
an attack." You know, stuff like that.
Basic
immediate threat information. Mhm. They
don't like each other. They don't trust
each other. They cooperate when they
absolutely have to cooperate. But, as as
for
joint operations, especially lethal
operations, absolutely not.
Uh Will Will over on the Rumble feed,
thanks for the $2. I was kind of
disappointed that Turkey issues
they still have a plan a chance to play
a role there?
>> You know, I was actually surprised that
that the Turks filed these charges. They
know that nothing's going to come of
these charges. They know that no
country's going to snatch Netanyahu and
turn him over to the ICC.
I was surprised because, you're right,
Turkey had been discussed
very recently
as
being one of those countries that that
that likely would play a large role in
Gaza, whether it was peacekeeping or
redevelopment or whatever.
And now, I mean, politically the
Israelis are going to have to keep the
Turks out. I'm not really sure why they
did that, unless it was just a kind of a
cynical move by Erdogan to to shore up
his um his conservative base. Otherwise,
I don't see what the Turks get out of
making a decision like that.
Jennifer PO points out about French
criminal law, procedure is traditionally
written presented as written, secret,
and non-adversarial.
But, this law was changed a long time
ago.
Yeah, so maybe that's like that's why
it's still in the Dreyfus affair affair
movie. Um Jennifer continues, "There was
no presumption of in of innocence in
France when your dad lived there,
grandfather, actually. But, post-2002,
thanks to the Guigou law, uh named after
Elisabeth Guigou, that has changed."
time.
Um
Let's let's see. Uh
Let's see. Oh,
there was some couple there are a couple
of questions if you don't mind.
>> Yes, please. That's what I wanted to get
to. There there's an easy one first. Um
John, another SEAL Team Six guy came
forward from the UBL raid and gave more
praise to Alfreda Bikowsky. Did you ever
work with her? If so, was she as good as
described? I worked
hand in glove with Alfreda Bikowsky. She
was my immediate boss when I was the
chief of the counterintelligence branch
at the uh Alex Station.
Um
I don't want to say too much. My own
personal belief, is she that good? Yeah,
if the if the point is to
is to kill people, yes, she's very good
at killing people.
Um I believe that she was a monster. I
believe that Alfreda was guilty of
crimes against humanity, and I don't I
don't use the term lightly. Um
I would not want Alfreda coming after me
if I were
you know, an Arab.
Uh because you're going to end up on a
slab in a morgue.
Uh but
Alfreda is not not my cup of tea.
Uh that was number one. The other one
was, "Hey guys, I have a two-part
question for you both. How do you guys
follow the news? What medium do you use?
And how do you analyze it? How do you
find all the outcomes and sift through
them?"
You [snorts] want to You want to tackle
that one first?
>> Sure. Um yeah, I mean, in in my case, uh
main- mainly I read the news on my
phone. I I go through um you know, I
everything every news source that's
basically free and in the English or
French languages, I scan every day. Um
sort of my generic is the Google News,
but then I'll look at AP, uh Reuters,
The Guardian, uh
TF124, the French uh TV network. Um I
think it's always good to have a the
foreign uh thing. Always got to do the
New York Times, Wall Street Journal, uh
well, you know, Washington Post, New
York Post is actually an important
source. Um
And uh you know, I try I I do not really
do social media. A lot of people are
getting their news through social media
feeds. I just don't trust it. I find
like there's too much much to get
through. I'm old. I'm 62 years old. So,
for me, I I like I still look at branded
news outlets. And then like how do I
analyze it? Um my brain kind of has you
know, I remember we learned like in the
1970s, John, that like Soviet citizens
like learned to read between the lines,
and they would compare like Yes. to
Izvestia and look Yes.
the [clears throat] consistencies and
the inconsistency. And you And that's
sort of what you have to do now because
it's you know, it's always as we you and
I talked about on your old show when I
guested on it, um is that it's not what
they say, it's what they don't say. It's
always what they leave out, right? Yeah.
There there's a always stuff that's like
context-free, historic free of his of
history that that they just don't
mention. And so to me, it's about I have
a good memory, and I remember most of
what I've read, and I and it and I can
compare it. So
that said, I'm sure I'm being lied to
and falling for some lies, no question
about it.
That's my That's my short answer. I
uh do just about the same as Ted. I
actually get up every morning early just
so I could read the papers. I'll tell
you where I start. Um I start with
Google News, then I go to the
Washington Post, Wall Street Journal,
New York Times, LA Times, Pittsburgh
Post-Gazette. Don't criticize me. I know
it's a right-wing paper and they're on
strike. Then I go to CNN, Associated
Press, Fox, Politico, The Hill, the New
York Post. Then I read the Greek papers,
and then I read um well, the Telegraph
and The Guardian. The Telegraph I have I
actually have a subscription to. The
London Evening Standard. Then I check
some of the lesser ones, uh Raw Story,
BBC, Al Jazeera, Al Monitor, Electronic
Intifada. And then I look to see what my
friends are writing at Consortium News.
And I've got Axios there in case
something's breaking. They're They
oftentimes break um
new news.
And then I'm ready for the show.
Gregory Batiste CFA, thanks for the five
bucks and the laugh. Uh here's five
bucks for a copy of the LA Times for
Ted. [laughter]
Mhm. Well, my my my ass is a little
itchy, so I probably missed some spots
this morning, so thank you for that. And
some poppy seeds for John. Uh Evil Robot
>> Just what I need for my next drug test.
No, I'm not drug tested anymore. Just
kidding.
>> Evil Robot Army, five bucks. Thank you
for that. What do What do we What do we
think about Gavin Newsom? When AIPAC was
mentioned on The Young Turks a few weeks
ago, haven't heard you mention it.
I I didn't see him on The Young Turks.
I've I've got a bias against Gavin
Newsom. I think he has DNC written all
over him. I think he's sort of faking
things right now to make himself look
like he's kind of an independent
progressive. I don't trust the guy. I
don't like him. I don't like that
Hollywood smile that he has. I hate that
he banged his best friend's wife. Not
cool at all.
But so far, he's pretty much all the
Democrats have.
Totally agree with that, and I have a
personal grudge against Gavin Newsom cuz
he [__] me in the LA Times.
>> he did.
Um
Dr. Strangelove7739,
John, can the CIA pressure American
businessmen who live overseas to
cooperate in spying against a foreign
country?
>> Of course, and they do it every day.
Absolutely yes. That's why they have
this thing called the National Resources
Division. They go up to you and they
say, "Listen, you're American, we're
CIA, you're a patriot, we really need
for you to do X, Y, and Z for us." They
always say yes.
So yeah, that's that's an easy one. Oh,
yeah.
Why do they always say yes? Why wouldn't
they say No one ever says, "I'm familiar
with the history of your agency and how
you burn people, and I don't want to be
burned, so thank you, but no, thank
you."
>> See, that's what you and I would say.
But people think it's cool, it's
clandestine, it's exciting. You can
whisper to your buddies, you know, over
beers, "Hey, the CIA approached me. I'm
working with them right now on this cool
thing." They always say yes. Ego. Yep.
Uh Scary Girl, um
okay, sorry, that that's an accidental
one. Oh, uh
is there any chance of the French
monarchy being restored? No.
>> [laughter]
>> Same with the Greek monarchy.
How come?
First of all, they didn't even speak
Greek.
Oh, where are they from? From Denmark.
That's it
Monarchy is so European monarchy is so
strange, right? Could you imagine a
scenario where say the the emperor of
China is from, you know, Vietnam. Like,
no.
>> [laughter]
>> No. Or the Philippines.
>> No. But but
royalty was imposed on Greece
uh in in 1821 upon um the uh the start
of the revolution against the Ottoman
Empire. And uh the first king of Greece
was named Otto. As which isn't even a
Greek name. They had to Hellenize it by
calling him Othonas, which is the Greek
version of Otto. He was Bavarian. He was
a minor minor German prince.
Um he was a cousin of Queen Victoria.
So, they put him on the throne.
We hated him. He was king for like 30
years, never bothered to learn how to
speak Greek. So, he would give his
pronouncements in German and have a
translator translate it. He finally went
on vacation to Germany one year, and the
Greeks told him, "Don't bother coming
back because if you do, we're going to
hang you from a tree."
And so he never came back. So then,
Queen Victoria
>> a mistake when you're a monarch to leave
the country.
>> Always. So, Queen Victoria imposed
another king on us. Um this was a a
minor Danish prince, became king of
Greece. Um
he actually was
he served for a long time. His son
became the king. His son was bitten by a
monkey.
Uh he was he was in Thessaloniki. This
guy had a pet monkey. The king said,
"Can I pet your monkey?" He went to pet
him. The monkey bit him.
And the the bite got infected, and he
died of sepsis.
That's so [__] weird.
>> [laughter]
>> So, his brother became the king,
promptly got the Greeks in World War I
on the wrong side.
Um it's a long story, but finally in
1967,
when the military junta overthrow the
overthrew the democratic government,
they also overthrew the royal family.
The royal family fled first to well,
first to Cairo, then Rome, and then they
settled in London. When I was living in
London, I would see the king
the exiled king in the front row, the
front pew at church. And there were
these rules like you can't talk to the
king. I was like, "I don't want to talk
to the freaking king. I don't I don't
believe in royalty." So, I never said
anything. Well, you don't believe that
God personally annoys some random [__]
to take over a country. Yeah, sorry, but
no, I sure don't. So, um
the the royal family there was a
plebiscite, a national referendum in
1975 after the military was overthrown,
and Greece reinstated its dem- its
democracy. Um
and the royal family got I forget, 10%?
5%? Something like that.
So, they did away with the with the
royal family, and they confiscated all
of their property, which was a really
nice move.
And so now they're renovating the
weekend palace. It's called Tatoi.
That's where they're all they're all
buried there. So, and it's it's just in
a state of complete just breakdown,
chaos, you know, trees growing through
cracks in the tombstones and stuff like
that. So, they're going to make it nice.
And And just in the last couple of years
they decided to allow former royal
family members to visit on tourist
visas.
And that's it. And then they can get the
hell out cuz they're not welcome.
It's all Yeah. See, I wouldn't That
That's a move I wouldn't have made if I
were the Greek government.
>> Really? Yeah, it's like, you know, it's
like
you guys do you can we like you better
somewhere else outside of Greece. I mean
Yeah. I mean they're
they're you know, they're they are a
objectively a little bit of a danger,
right? Uh Longhorn Clemens is asking if
we're going to
name and shame Robbie's employer
>> Ah, good question.
>> we may choose not to do business with
them in the future. I'm just going to
without giving it away, I don't think
that they're the kind of business that
we would you would probably be likely to
come into contact with. But we'll leave
that to Robbie to answer that question.
It seems to me like vengeance is best
served by the person who was aggrieved.
Um also Do we Do we Oh, better
Thanksgiving Yeah, Fuso Buck, better
Thanksgiving dinner, Charlie Brown or
Trump Walmart?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know what Trump Walmart means.
I gave my second son $5 once
and I asked him to go to the Walmart
meat counter and ask if where where he
could find the turducken.
And just to watch the guy's face like,
what?
So, I was able to take a picture, yeah.
>> Grossest idea. It might be really yummy.
>> Constantine asking for a turducken. I
don't like duck though, so I don't want
the and I don't like turkey.
So, yeah. I barely like chicken. I
Indian chicken.
>> Robbie's got a question. John, can you
say Greece is democratic when it arrests
for speech? I'll pass. Uh yeah, I I I
call it democratic. Um of course. Now, I
will admit to you that in today's
uh edition of Kathimerini, there's an
article that Greece is now 88th in the
world in terms of press freedom up from
107th, but still last in the European
Union. And part of that is they do not
allow pro-Nazi hate speech. That's what
the fight is about. So, you know,
is it Is it democratic? Of course it is.
It has 36 different political parties,
six or seven of which are represented in
parliament. Uh just cuz they don't allow
the Nazis to spew their hate. And this
is a country that lost more
people
per capita like
as a percentage of the country's
population
of any country in the world
during the Second World War. So, yeah.
I say they're democratic. Oh, Fraz
Matraz, I think maybe I made myself
unclear. He says he's surprised that we
trust he or she that we trust Trump over
Rashid Dostum, the Uzbek warlord.
>> thought that's what you said. That's not
what I said at all. I trust Dostum. Oh,
I I trust Trump more than Dostum.
I mean,
Dostum
Dostum never lied to me.
And Dostum told me a some uncomfortable
truths that um
Wow.
Dostum, if I had been in the room with
Dostum, it would have taken all my
energy not to shoot him in the brain.
Uh it took it took my all my energy to
not like die of of fear. Um
>> [laughter]
>> I mean, I was absolutely terrified, you
know? But I mean, he he had no reason to
be to do
>> to me, but that
>> if the
But if the mood had struck him
Yeah.
Yeah. No, he's he's absolutely a
psychopath. No question about it.
>> Without any doubt. Um I mean, it's kind
of like, you know, what is a psychopath?
Let's uh
Let's go take a look at that. Um You're
welcome, Fraz Matraz. All right, well, I
think we're we're winding Oh, well, God,
we got to talk Maybe we'll get around to
this tomorrow. Um so,
uh Israeli Israel's ITV um basically has
a documentary. It's sort of like the
Winter Soldier for Israel. Um and
basically uh they have a bunch of
IDF troops admitting Yes. uh it was a
free fire zone in Gaza. And now, of
course, they're suffering from PTSD. Of
course they are. They did terrible
things.
>> back and either and and basically they
were they forced Palestinians into into
tunnels that were mined uh in order to
map them out. They did all sorts of [__]
that was just absolutely crazy. None of
this is surprising. No. But it's good
that it's coming out. It's actually
probably good for the mental health of
[snorts] the soldiers who are the
veterans who are coming forward.
>> And I'm going to make a prediction. It's
going to come out more and more and more
and we're going to see that all the
stuff that ICRC said or Human Rights
Watch or Amnesty International
that it's all going to end up being
true.
And we're going to see more and more
Israeli whistleblowers. Mark my words.
It's going to come.
>> No question.
>> [snorts]
>> All right. Well, with that,
um we're going to go ahead and call it a
show. We'll be back uh tomorrow as we
always are, Monday through Friday, 9:00
a.m. Eastern Time. Thank you so much for
joining us. John, always a pleasure.
Good to see you, Ted. And uh we will
talk to you then. Thanks for tuning in.
Please stay tuned for the TMI show with
Ted Rall and Manila Chan, that's me. Uh
for a lighter take on the news, we've
got some fun stories including the fact
that the Trump administration doesn't
want to let fat people into the United
States on tourist visas anymore.
>> [snorts]
>> Strange but true. No.
Bye, everybody. Bye.